(Leonard:)She doesn't like you.
- Well, you have a gall bladder to remove.
- Yeah.
(Leonard:)And I have to get in the shower
and Penny has clothes to put on, so...
- Well, it was very nice meeting you.
- Nice to finally meet you too.
- I'll see you tonight? Bye.
- Yeah. Bye-bye.
(Sheldon:)What could I possibly have done to offend
Mrs. Vartabedian?
(Penny:)So that's Stephanie, huh?
(Leonard:)Why do I feel like I'm the one
that just got the prostate exam?
- You know, she seems very nice.
- Oh, she is. She's terrific.
(Sheldon:)And she's proving to be
a valuable roommate.
- Roommate? You guys are living together?
- Like hippies.
(Leonard:)We're not living together.
(Sheldon:)Do I have to pull out
the paperwork again?